<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CarnoSpace Mission Planner</string>
    <string name="mission_list">Command center</string>
    <string name="mission_details">Mission control</string>

    <string name="action_help">Huston, we have a problem!</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="close_about">Close</string>
    <string name="close_help">Got it!</string>

    <!-- ingame text -->
    <string name="difficulty_display">Diff. %d</string>
    <string name="payload_display">Payload: %d</string>
    <string name="rockets_list_display">Required rockets: %s</string>
    <string name="rockets_mass_display">Mass: %d</string>

    <!-- long formatted text -->
    <string name="about_text"><big><b>CarnoSpace Mission Planner</b></big>\n
        \nUtility application for Leaving Earth; mission planning made easy!\n
        \nReleased under the <a href="https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.en.html">GNU General Public License V3</a>\n
        \nApplication made by <a href="http://www.twitter.com/need2revolt">Need2Revolt</a>\n
        \nFind source code of this app at:\n
        <a href="https://github.com/Need2Revolt/LEMP">https://github.com/Need2Revolt/LEMP</a>\n
        <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Need2Revolt/lemp/">https://bitbucket.org/Need2Revolt/lemp/</a>\n
        \nAll Leaving Earth related stuffs are copyright of <a href="https://www.lumenaris.com/about.html">The Lumenaris Group inc.</a>\n
        \nFAB icons made by <a href="http://www.flaticon.com/authors/eucalyp">Eucalyp</a>
        and by <a href="http://www.flaticon.com/authors/smartline">Smartline</a>
        from <a href="http://www.flaticon.com">www.flaticon.com</a>,  licensed
        by <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/">CC 3.0 BY</a>
        \n
        \n
    </string>

    <string name="help_text">
        <big><b>Lost in space?</b></big>
        \n\n
        <b>Remember, this is still beta stuff</b>
        \n\n
        If you haven\'t read Leaving Earth rulebook, go do it now and then come back here. This application is a digital
        version of the mission tables from the rulebook, with some automations.
        \n\n
        As the first thing, create a mission from <b>\"Command Center\"</b> view
        using the floating button. Then choose a mission name, it can either be something that reminds you
        what the goal is, like <b>\"Man to Moon\"</b> or some fancy and secret name if you fear other space
        agencies espionage, like <b>\"Seeliger Effect\"</b>. You\'ll see some information about the mission,
        the most important one is the total cost that will be auto-calculated for you.
        \n\n
        Now the next step is to add mission stages, just like the rulebook explains, in reverse order.
        Tap on a mission and the <b>\"Mission control\"</b> view will open. Click on the floating
        button to add a stage of your spacecraft. The first stage that you add will be the last one that
        you\'ll use. Give a name to the stage like <b>\"Moon lander\"</b>, or a description with
        all the necessary pieces you need, like <b>\"Moon lander: eagle capsule, Aldrin, 2x supply, take sample\"</b>.
        Total mass for the next stage will be auto-calculated, so from now on just enter the difficulty.
        Keep adding all the stages required until you reach the launch of your mission.
        \n\n
        At this point you\'ll have the optimal combination of rockets for each stage/maneuver in the current list.
        If you go back to Command Center, you\'ll also have a total cost for the mission.
        \n\n
        If you decide to abort a mission, long tap on it and a menu will popup allowing you to delete it.
        Deletion is not recoverable, so think twice if you want to have a log of all your mission during
        several games.
        \n\n
        That\'s it!

    </string>
</resources>
